googmark.in 2016-10-23

# Privacy Policy And Disclaimer

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When registering for the feeds in our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Children**

This site respects the sensitive nature of childrens privacy online. We do not direct any of our content or services, not do we knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under thirteen, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to this site through the Site, please contact us and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Disclaimer**

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by this site and whilst we endeavor to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website. Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of us. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them. Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, we takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

**Amazon Disclaimer**

CERTAIN CONTENT THAT APPEARS COMES FROM AMAZON SERVICES LLC. THIS CONTENT IS PROVIDED AS IS AND IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE OR REMOVAL AT ANY TIME. This site is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com or any other website that may be affiliated to Amazon Service LLC Associate Program.
